This horrifying game is The Night Cage.
Acest joc infiorător este The Night Cage.
You and your friends have woke up in a bottomless dark pit with only a candle.
Tu și prietenii tăi vă treziți într-o groapă fără fund întunecată, doar cu o lumânare.
Your goal is to find the key and escape this labyrinth before the darkness consumes you.
Scopul vostru este să găsiți cheia și să scăpați din acest labirint înainte ca întunericul să vă consume.
Every turn you'll be moving around the labyrinth and illuminating the paths around you.
La fiecare tură te vei mișca în labirint și vei lumina căile din jurul tău.
As you light up new areas, old ones will fade away,
Pe măsură ce luminezi zone noi, cele vechi vor dispărea,
creating a new path for anyone that comes across it.
creând o nouă cale pentru oricine o descoperă.
Eventually, you'll find a room with a skeleton key. You'll grab it and make your run for the escape.
La un moment dat, vei găsi o cameră cu o cheie-schelet. O vei lua și vei alerga spre ieșire.
It sounds simple enough, except there's something evil that dwells in this labyrinth.
Sună destul de simplu, însă ceva malefic trăiește în acest labirint.
Every time you're hit, you'll lose time in the labyrinth and your candle will burn out,
De fiecare dată când ești lovit, vei pierde timp în labirint și lumânarea ta se va stinge,
leaving you in the darkness to walk blindly, not knowing what horrors lie ahead.
lăsându-te în întuneric să mergi orbește, neștiind ce orori te așteaptă.
And every type of monster is different. Some of them will hold the keys in their stomach,
Fiecare tip de monstru e diferit. Unii dintre ei vor ține cheile în stomacurile sale,
others will destroy paths and turn them into pits,
alții vor distruge drumuri și le vor transforma în gropi,
and even a colossal being that can take away from the space in this labyrinth.
și chiar o ființă colosala care va putea ocupa o mare parte din spațiul labirintului.
Now if you're able to make it to the gate with all 4 keys, then you'll be able to escape,
Daca reușiți să ajungeți la poarta de ieșire cu toate cele 4 chei, atunci veți putea scăpa,
but if time runs out, or you're not able to collect enough keys,
dar dacă timpul va expira sau nu veți strânge suficiente chei,
then your candle will fade out and you'll be consumed by this darkness...
atunci lumânarea se va stinge complet și veți fi consumați de acest întuneric...